Suddenly, an expedition!
Hello! My name is Shinji Kikise!
I'm Shinji Kikise!
I'm Shinji Kikise, and I'm a member of the "Suddenly Explorers" group!
Today, Shinji is alone.
Usually, we have a team of two to explore.
But I'm getting used to the two of us now.
I'm thinking of going on location so that I can go on my own.
So today, Shinju-san will be exploring by himself.
So today, Shinju-san is going to explore three kittens.
It's a vintage clothing store on the first basement floor of eBeans, isn't it?
I'll have you explore by yourself today. How do you like vintage clothing, Shinju-san?
I don't think I wear much.
I see. Pearl's vintage clothing coordinate.
I'm thinking of having you do it. Let's go to the store and explore first.
Okay. Let's go.
Here we are at the store. Three kittens.
There's a lot of clothes here. We're already on the first basement floor of Evin's.
We've been here for a long time. We're going to look at vintage clothes.
As Pearl mentioned earlier, you don't usually wear vintage clothing, so I'm sure there's a lot you don't know.
So I'm going to ask the store staff about it and see what they have to offer.
The manager went out of his way to come with me today. Shall I call him right away?
Hello.
I'm the manager of Kaneko's store in Miki.
I'm Vintage Sujiko. Pleased to meet you.
No problem at all.
Vintage Sujiko, the manager.
They call me Tara-chan.
Excuse me.
You're very peculiar, Mr. Manager.
Tara-chan.
Manager, are you wearing this tag?
It's all the rage these days.
It's a fashion trend these days. They dare to wear it and not take it off.
It's like finding your own value.
I see... I see... I can learn a lot from this.
That's great.
I'd like to go around the store a bit.
So today, I'd like to ask Jiko-san to come up with a vintage clothing line for me.
I'll make a pitch for you.
I'd like to do it today.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
I'd like to go on a vintage clothing tour immediately.
Yay!
Tension. It's very unique and cool.
This is cleaning.
That's cool.
What's this corner?
What's the corner where the actors from overseas used to wear?
The corner where foreign actors used to wear?
It's all sold out.
If you look closely, you can smell the perfume.
Wow!
It's the duty-free section, right?
Yes, it is.
Men's stuff.
Oh, so you're from overseas.
It's so vintage.
It's a recent fad that's going around the times.
I see... I see...
There are many kinds.
Why do you hang your clothes from the ceiling like this?
By absorbing the outside air from above.
As it absorbs the air from above, it becomes richer in protein.
It's a starch effect.
It's to make them stand out, isn't it?
That's part of it.
On the surface, yes, but...
But the outside air from above...
Outside air from above? It's underground.
The air makes our skin better.
Our skin?
Our skin is old clothes.
It doesn't work like that.
It's dyed.
Wow, that's a new one.
I learned something else, didn't I?
Yes, yes.
But sweatshirts like this...
Like the ones for the basketball team.
Really cool.
You don't wear these? Shin-san.
I don't wear them.
They look good on you.
What? Harajuku? This is Harajuku?
It looks good on you.
Really?
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
I'm glad.
I'm sure it would look great on a woman or a man.
Even if it's a little bigger.
It's totally possible.
It's fine.
Oversized?
Yes, yes.
Do you know what's in style these days?
The latest trend is to wear street-style clothes that are loose-fitting.
Men's style is really cute because it's oversized when worn.
That's for sure.
Let me introduce you to some of the manager's recommendations.
I recommend this red one.
I'm wearing it right now.
Yes, yes, yes.
I wonder what kind of terry cloth it's made of.
Wow.
You call it a terrorem shirt?
Terrorist shirt.
Is it called a terroir shirt?
Yes, it's called a terroir shirt.
Yes, the Terror Shirt is a little popular.
I just picked one up, Shinii-san.
What do you recommend?
Let me guess...
I see...
You've got your eyes closed, right, Sujiko?
I can tell by that.
Wow.
Wouldn't it be faster to look?
No, I choose by feel.
I see.
Fashion is all about sensibility.
You're making your selections while wrapping them up in a really nice package.
I see.
Is this it?
Wow!
I hope it continues to spread its wings.
But you don't usually wear this kind of thing, do you?
No, I don't.
But I like red.
That's the player of Mr. Surgia!
I saw this on Wikipedia.
It says you like red.
You've learned a lot in advance, haven't you?
So, do you want to put it in today's outfit?
Yes.
I'd like to wear it with a kerchief.
This one.
A kerchief.
Next
Pants
We have to go around here.
Why?
We're going back where we came from.
We have to go around.
We all have to go around.
Do you have anything?
Yes, we do.
It's the Sujiko way.
This is what the Sujiko Channel is wearing.
Sujiko Channel.
I call myself "Sujiko Channel".
It's a pain in the ass, isn't it?
Tara-chan is surrounded by people
Like this...
I think it's good.
Do you think it fits?
Do you wear pants?
I don't really wear pants.
I don't think so.
You look cute.
And these...
I'm sorry, I can't see the color.
It's a little fresh.
I'm not sure which one I like better.
What do you think?
Me?
I'll take the check.
This one?
This one then.
Hey, Sujiko.
Aren't you going to coordinate?
We have to respect each other.
Everyone's opinion counts.
It'll cause a firestorm.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
I'll go to the jerseys next time.
I have to go around again.
Are you okay with that?
It's like Dracula.
I have to follow the hero. What's this?
It's important.
Next, this way.
"Nine dead letters.
Next is this one.
Purple and blue.
This one...
It's like old clothes.
This makes me a little happy.
I see what you mean.
And this one.
Oh, nice and loud.
What's up with that? I'm just admiring your sense of style.
You've never worn a design like this before.
Which one do you like? This one?
I like this one! It's the best.
It's like a horse race jockey. Like a horse race jockey.
This one's good. What's wrong? What's wrong, Shinichi?
It's really nice. It's like this, depending on the dish.
It's the least fashionable.
It's stylish. I've never worn it before.
It's like vintage clothing. It's got red in it.
It's got a little bit of red in it. I think it matches the point of the dress.
It's a new look.
What's wrong with it? It's going straight. -One point.
You don't do this for everyone, do you?
I passed by it. It's this way.
Oh, the scarf.
This is it.
This one.
You chose this one.
I'll see you later.
Manager.
This is it.
What's up with that?
Oh no, wait a minute.
Tell the manager.
Manager
Yes, sir.
You look like a baby.
No, no, no. They grow up so fast.
Okay, next, the car tube.
Yes, car tube.
And a lot of little things.
You have a lot of accessories, Mr. Manager. Yes, a lot of accessories.
It's amazing.
I always thought so when I walked by here.
You were? You have a lot of knickknacks.
They have a lot of clips and stuff.
I'm wearing a clip here right now.
And it comes off? Yes.
That's what happens.
Girls love them.
Girls love this kind of thing.
They're great.
They don't look like anyone else's. Do you carry it with you all the time?
When I pass by. Really?
You can keep it till the end of the year.
I'm sure you'll have it next year.
We have a lot of catsuits.
Really! It's so cute!
These accessories are important for fashion, aren't they?
Yes, accessories are what set you apart from others.
I see.
This is a cartouche.
There are a lot of them, including this one.
That's right.
Try one of Pearl's favorites first.
Sure. What does the manager recommend?
Why don't you ask her what she recommends?
I like this one.
A pretty one.
Sure, sure.
This one or this one?
Okay, okay, okay.
What's wrong? Pearl.
I thought I did it.
Oh, which one do you like better?
Pearl's?
I'd say the one you have.
But, you know, today, the manager...
I'll leave it to him.
I agree. Let's go this way.
Let's take a ride. I'll wear the manager's outfit today.
I'll wear sunglasses.
It's going to be like we're twins.
There's something I have to do before I choose sunglasses.
What you have to do before choosing sunglasses
Two bow, two claps.
You're going to pray?
Yes, this way.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, please do it.
All the staff do it.
Pick out your sunglasses.
Oh.
Ooh.
Here you go.
What's this? It's a ritual for choosing sunglasses.
To the god of vintage clothing? Yes. I like the one who created vintage clothing in the first place.
I don't have bangs. I'm trying to melt them now. I don't have any more bangs.
Yes, that's right. There are many kinds.
I think Pearl's favorite will be fine in the end. Is that okay?
I like pink. If it's pink, it's this one. It's good, isn't it? If it's exactly the same, maybe this one.
Yes, Pearl, I'm glad you decided to match mine. Pearl, I came here to buy this.
I can't imagine this coordinate of pearls. I've never seen anything like this before. And is everything all right? I said I'll put a clip on it.
I'll put the clips on. Then I'll choose a clip at the end and we'll be done. I see.
Clip. I'll choose a clip at the end and complete the process. I see. A clip.
This is cute. Oh, this is cute.
I bought this from my dad's old clothes. You wear something like this? Sujiko's father.
This kind of quilted lining is popular in winter.
It's cute. You have this here, don't you?
What do you think this is used for? You're going to hook it, aren't you? No, it's not.
It's a ring. It's not in the way, is it? No, no. It doesn't get in the way when you walk?
It's like this, you put your arm through here. You don't want it to hang on your finger? It's weighted.
What are you doing? What are you doing? It's our fault. What are you doing?
It's M for Miu Miu, isn't it? That's right.
It's a Miu Miu M. It's a size, you know. It's Sujiko. He's doing "Miu Miu" or something.
Huh? No, it's not. It's different. No, it's not. I can understand S.
Straw, straw. Straw, straw. No, it's straw straw. The zone here is long. Indeed. I'm choosing a hair clip.
This one. It's cute.
Cute. Cute. Cute. Enough already. Enough.
Let's do this one. Here's a second one. I like bears. You have this kind of thing, too, don't you? Yes, they do. Cute.
Okay, that settles it. Shall we change? Yes, I'll change. I'll change. To change then.
Heh heh heh.
Okay, then, manager. That's exactly what you were doing.
Before I left, I was just getting dressed.
She's looking very pretty. Really?
Then let's have her make an appearance. Then I'll go.
Oh, wow!
Kira!
Get out of the way, manager!
So cute!
May I take a lap?
Oh, my gosh!
So cute!
Oh!
What do you think?
It's so cute!
More flashy than the manager!
I made it more flashy than the manager.
What do you think, Manager Sujiku?
I'd like to introduce some points here.
My favorite point is
The purple hair clip on her shoulder.
Purple hair clip
Really! You used it here?
Shinji, you have flowers in your heart.
You have flowers on your shoulders, too.
What's with that inquiry?
Also, this red butterfly wai-set
And this red butterfly wyeset
and this jersey that goes with it.
this stands out.
I see.
And the red butterfly on the outside of this jersey
Butterfly red.
This red thing is the
pattern
Very cute!
These orange pants are also
The silhouette is really beautiful
they look straight and
and slimming.
While Shinji was changing earlier
the manager is wearing these pants
I'm a customer.
Did I mention I bought them?
I knew it.
Something's gone wrong.
What was that?
I knew it.
Oh, and he's close.
I'll be with him tomorrow.
I see... charisma.
I'll come tomorrow.
I'm coming to buy this.
It's my store.
The point is to buy Shinji-chan's favorite
A bear!
And by having this
By having this kerchief
Straight hair and
black hair also looks good
by the colorful body shape.
I see. It suits you.
Fashion is what makes everyone unique.
The pelvis is also important in fashion.
The shape of your bones also makes a difference in fashion.
It also brings out the transparency of each person.
Therefore, fashion is truly a product of everyone's ideas and characteristics.
It's something that was created based on everyone's ideas and characteristics.
I think everyone should go home.
I think you should think about that when you go home.
Yes, Mr. Shinju!
Today, with three kittens
Manager Sujiko did it for me.
I had Manager Sujiko coordinate them for you.
How did you like it, Shinju-san?
Yes, she did a coordination that I wouldn't normally do.
That's for sure.
Next time I go backstage with this...
I'm sure the members would be surprised.
It's really cute!
I'm going to try my best to be the kind of person who looks good in this outfit.
I'm going to try my best to look good in this dress.
It does look good on me, though.
It does look good on you.
Thank you for today.
I'll see you later.
What's your name?
I don't know your name.
Sujiko.
Vintage Sujiko
Please make an announcement.
At the 3 kittens Evins store
We have a large amount of vintage autumn goods in stock!
I see
We certainly have a lot of great stuff.
I'd be happy if you could all come by and play with them while you're catting around.
That's right.
Only for cats.
Yes, that's right.
Please come and see our three kittens.
Please come!
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan
So you really made it as a manager.
When I did this at the interview, he got mad.
It's a very good company, isn't it?
Please give it a try.
It's fine.
See you next week.
Next week?
We're doing this every week?
Next week.
That's tough.
All right, that's it.
Thank you all very much.
Bye, bye, bye!
Boom, boom, boom!
Se-no!
meow
Meow
me eh